

# HO THIEN KHOI Software Engineer





Thu Duc District, HCM City



## **SUMMARY**

I have already had 5+years working experience in web application as a .NET Developer in Ominext Group Joint Stock Company, MUFG Bank and FPT Sofware HCM City. I have strong knowledge of technologies and techniques. High sense of responsibility, good working attitude and skills are main factors that help me promote my career. Knowledge has no boder, so I will never stop learning and improving myself. I am willing to seek new challenges and responsibilities. At last, to me, contributing to the company's development is the way to prove my abilities.



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **OMINEXT COMPANY - .NET TEAM**

Jan 2022 - Present

#### Developer

- \* Description
- 1. Build a project Web System as a cloud service with the aim of providing a health check-up system for medical facilities. This system has 2 main uses:
- For medical facilities for medical examination and for management of medical examination.
- For health examiners to use to register for the examination or confirm examination results, etc.
- \* Team size: 10+
- \* My position: Developer
- \* My responsibilities(Backend Developer):
- Create web API CRUD with Entity Framework and test it using swagger.
- Handle bugs and optimize flow code, review code for the new member in my team.
- \* Technologies used:
- C#, .Net Core 6.0, Web API, LINQ, SQL Server, HTML/CSS, Javascript, GIT.
- 2. Build a project Winform Application e-commerce management system.
- The main responsibilities are to perform warehouse management tasks: order, product delivery, issue invoices, and promotions.
- \* Team size: 20+
- \* My position: Developer
- \* My responsibilities:
- Coding functions of the screen in the design document.
- Create Stored Procedure in SQL
- \* Technologies used:
- C# WinForm, SQL, Linq, GIT.

### **MUFG BANK - IA TEAM**

May 2021 - Jan 2022

## Developer

- \* Description
- 1. Build a project Winform Application allow Staff to register, update working location every week in the context of covid 19.
- 2. Build project web aplication Account Maintenance Fee Tool to able to identify accounts that subjected to account maintenance fee.
- \* Team size: 4
- \* My position: Developer
- \* My responsibilities:
- Create APIs MVC in MVC
- Create Stored Procedure in SQL
- Manual Testing
- \* Technologies used
- C# Windows Forms, Web API MVC, AngularJS, LINQ, SQL Server

#### Developer

\* Description

There are many projects that were built and operated by GBOOK for over 10 years, the main goal is to maintain and enhance them. I am to develop new features into the current web application as required by customers of Toyota Japan.

- \* Team size: 25-30+
- \* My position: Developer (Includes 3 steps)
- Coding
- Write test cases in Software Testing
- Unit testing C# with NUnit
- \* My responsibilities
- Maintenance and enhancement
- \* Technologies used:
- C#, .NET MVC, .NET core 3.1, LINQ, SQL Server

### FPT SOFWARE HCM - DMS TEAM

April 2018 - August 2018

#### Developer

- \* Description:
- Comprehensive Distribution Solutions ERP for UNIBEN & PEPSI
- \* Team size: 12-15+
- \* My position: Developer
- \* Programming Languages: Microsoft Dynamics NAV 365
- \* IDE: Microsoft Dynamics NAV 365
- \* Used technologies: Packages Dynamic Navision



## **Education**

### POSTS AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Oct 2013 - May 2018

Major: Software Technology

GPA: 2.3/4